<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name> !Szx Chinese Console</name>
    <directory>szx_chinese_console</directory>
    <id>3001774454</id>
    <description>The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
-----------------------------------------------------------------
这是一个拥有诸多功能的控制台mod！
（v2.24更新：若安装了IsaacSocket，打开三只熊中文控制台界面时游戏会完全暂停）
（v2.21更新：你无需将全屏[F]、静音[M]、暂停[P]三个按键改为[F9][F10][F11]，输入指令时不再触发全屏、静音、暂停效果）
（v2.03更新：你无需在option.ini文件中把以撒的官方控制台关闭，也可以正常使用本控制台mod）

具体的控制台功能详情，可以来看我的b站视频，视频讲解地会比较细致，也更加容易理解~

有任何问题欢迎联系我，祝大家玩的愉快！

更新日志：

v2.27更新
优化了部分搜索栏界面显示逻辑
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，可以使用电脑中文输入法输入任何字或词(只要该字符在字体库中就会显示)
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，可以进入三只熊中文控制台主界面第四页，增加了四条额外指令，包括修改伊甸币数量、新建调试控制台、释放调试控制台、输出文字至调试控制台

v2.26更新
增加了使用[LAlt]+[num1-9或num0]快捷操作后的顶部提示信息
增加了rep或repeat指令生效后的提示信息，包括指令内容与生效次数
修复了rep或repeat指令在开启新的一局游戏后失效的问题
修复了rep或repeat指令在IsaacSocket安装时不能正确执行用户期望指令的问题
修复了[LAlt]+[num1-9或num0]快捷操作在IsaacSocket安装时不能正确执行用户期望指令的问题
适配最新的IsaacSocket连接程序，优化部分代码逻辑
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，在官方控制台内按[LCtrl+c]也会复制当前文字(在三只熊中文控制台内按[LCtrl+c]同样会复制当前文字)
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，在游戏内暂停菜单也可以按[`]呼出三只熊控制台
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，[stage]指令和[giveitem k],[g k],[giveitem2 k],[g2 k]指令会立刻执行，与官方控制台效果一致(若您未安装IsaacSocket则所有指令均会立即执行，因为游戏不会暂停)

v2.25更新
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，现在lua语句、luamod语句和lualua指令也会在三只熊中文控制台界面立刻执行(游戏完全暂停)

v2.24更新
增加[F1][LAlt+F1][F2][LAlt+F2][F3][F4][F5][F6][Ins]按下后的顶部文字显示
增加在三只熊中文控制台内[LCtrl+c]按下后的顶部文字显示(该复制功能需要安装IsaacSocket实现)
取消[F6][Ins]和控制台内[LCtrl+c]按下后的角色快乐/悲伤动画
现在起若安装了IsaacSocket，打开三只熊中文控制台界面时游戏会完全暂停

v2.23更新
由于以撒官方游戏漏洞，导致无法捕获和改变“加入2p”这个操作，手柄玩家在输入指令后按[Enter]键仍然会召唤出2p玩家或2p宝宝的问题暂时无法解决，手柄玩家建议使用[小键盘Enter]来输入指令
现在即便大退以撒游戏，重载本模组，甚至游戏崩溃，历史指令仍然会被保存(按[上]键调用)
现在开启一局新的游戏或长按r键不再清空显示框内的历史文字信息
现在#d3、#d4、#d8、#d9、#d10的文字显示是否开启不再随着每一局新游戏而默认启动，而是会保存设置（仍然按[Ins]键打开/关闭）
现在长按[Tab]显示道具品质是否开启不再随着每一局新游戏而默认启动，而是会保存设置（仍然在打开控制台时按[F6]键打开/关闭）
现在键盘映射是否开启不再随着每一局新游戏而默认启动，而是会保存设置（仍然在打开控制台时按[F4]键打开/关闭）
现在如果本模组在游戏内被重载，控制台种类会和重载前保持一致而不是默认的三只熊中文控制台
增加了&quot;lualua&quot;指令，若安装了IsaacSocket将调用其ReloadLua()函数，即重置lua环境
修复了有时输入中文打不了字或者光标不能正确移动的问题

更早的版本更新将在讨论区中展示

由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
-----------------------------------------------------------------
Changelog:

v2.27 update (last update)
Optimized the display logic for some search bar interfaces.
From now on, if IsaacSocket is installed, you can use the Chinese keyboard of the computer system to input any character or word (as long as the character is in the font library, it will be displayed).
From now on, if IsaacSocket is installed, you can access the fourth page of Szx Chinese Console main interface, which adds four additional commands, including modifying the amount of Eden Tokens, allocating a debug console, releasing the debug console, and outputting text to the debug console.

v2.26 update
Added top prompts for [LAlt]+[num1-9 or num0] opration.
Added prompts for the effective use of the 'rep' or 'repeat' command, including the command content and the number of times it has been effective.
Fixed the issue where the 'rep' or 'repeat' command becomes ineffective after starting a new game.
Fixed the issue where the 'rep' or 'repeat' command does not correctly execute user-expected commands when IsaacSocket is installed.
Fixed the issue where the [LAlt]+[num1-9 or num0] operation does not correctly execute user-expected commands when IsaacSocket is installed.
Adapted to the latest IsaacSocket connection program and optimized some code logic.
From now on, if IsaacSocket is installed, pressing [LCtrl+c] in the official console will copy the current text. (In Szx Chinese Console, pressing [LCtrl+c] will also copy the current text.)
From now on, if IsaacSocket is installed, Szx Chinese Console interface can be opened even in the in-game pause menu by pressing [`].
From now on, if IsaacSocket is installed, the [stage] command and [giveitem k], [g k], [giveitem2 k], [g2 k] commands will execute immediately, consistent with the official console. (If you do not have IsaacSocket installed, all commands will execute immediately because the game will not pause.)

Previous Updates in English will be shown in the whole mod description.

The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.</description>
    <version>1.37</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Pills"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Babies"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
