<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name> !Szx Chinese Console</name>
    <directory>szx_chinese_console</directory>
    <id>3001774454</id>
    <description>The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
-----------------------------------------------------------------
这是一个拥有诸多功能的控制台mod！
（v2.24更新：若安装了IsaacSocket，打开三只熊中文控制台界面时游戏会完全暂停）
（v2.21更新：你无需将全屏[F]、静音[M]、暂停[P]三个按键改为[F9][F10][F11]，输入指令时不再触发全屏、静音、暂停效果）
（v2.03更新：你无需在option.ini文件中把以撒的官方控制台关闭，也可以正常使用本控制台mod）

具体的控制台功能详情，可以来看我的b站视频，视频讲解地会比较细致，也更加容易理解~

有任何问题欢迎联系我，祝大家玩的愉快！

更新日志：

v3.03更新
修复了[F5]测试模式在忏悔+版本导致游戏崩溃的问题

v3.02更新
扩充了中文输入字库

v3.01更新
增加了[ls]查看种子记录和[ds]删除部分种子记录的指令（现在起三只熊中文控制台会记录每一局游戏的种子，以及对应的游戏模式和开局角色（包括mod角色））
增加了调整控制台位置、键盘映射位置、debug文字位置的功能（[F6]功能选项菜单内）
增加了[F6]功能选项菜单及其各级子菜单中的恢复默认按键
增加了开关控制台打印文字淡出的功能选项设置（[F6]功能选项菜单内）
修复了使用[F7]快速输入的&quot;ban &quot;指令在移动光标时出现的报错问题

v2.36更新
修复了[debug]或[d]指令传入参数不合法时的报错问题
修复了[dnt]和[gdnt]指令清空游戏内置计数器的问题

v2.35更新
修复了在三只熊中文控制台内输入本应显示报错信息的部分lua命令在输入后报错信息不显示并引起额外报错的问题

v2.34更新
优化了右上角实际游戏速度的显示逻辑
修复了在IsaacSocket运行时长按键盘输入文字过快的问题
适配最新的IsaacSocket连接程序

v2.33更新
修复了在三只熊中文控制台界面读取历史指令的操作中可能出现的报错问题
修复了修改游戏速度指令[speed]在1.0以上游戏速度可能失效的问题
查看解锁/未解锁成就指令[vac]的显示文字增加一次换行
增加了快速还原游戏速度按键[Ins](过快或过慢的游戏速度将难以使用控制台还原游戏速度)
增加了右上角实际游戏速度的显示（若使用了[speed]指令）
适配最新的IsaacSocket连接程序

v2.32更新
更改了三只熊中文控制台主界面[F6]效果，现在起[F6]为功能选项菜单
增加了底座道具的道具池显示功能，在[F6]功能选项菜单中可以开关此选项
取消了[Ins]快捷键，并将其效果合并入[F6]功能选项菜单中
更改了部分搜索栏文字
优化了修改捐款数量、修改贪婪捐款数量的逻辑，便于用户理解
增加了一个额外指令：修改游戏速度(需要安装IsaacSocket)

v2.31更新
现在起开启新的一局游戏不再将搜索框语言重置为英文
增加了修改捐款数量、修改贪婪捐款数量，共两个指令(需要安装IsaacSocket)

更早的版本更新将在讨论区中展示

由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
-----------------------------------------------------------------
Changelog:

v3.03 update (last update)
Fixed an issue where entering test mode by pressing [F5] caused the game to crash in Repentance+.

v3.02 update
Expanded characters in Chinese input mode.

v3.01 update
Added the commands [ls] to view seed records and [ds] to delete partial seed records (from now on, Szx Chinese Console will record the seed, game mode, and starting character (including mod characters) for each game).
Added features to adjust the position of the console, keyboard overlay, and debug texts (available in the [F6] functional options menu).
Added a &quot;reset to default&quot; button in the [F6] function options menu and all its submenus.
Added an option to toggle console text fade-out (available in the [F6] functional options menu).
Fixed an error that occurred when moving the cursor while using the [F7] quick input &quot;ban &quot; command.

v2.36 update
Fixed the issue where the [debug] or [d] command would throw an error when invalid parameters were passed.
Fixed the issue where the [dnt] and [gdnt] commands would reset the in-game counters.

v2.35 update
Fixed an issue in Szx Chinese Console where certain Lua commands that were supposed to display error messages did not show the error messages and caused additional errors after being entered.

v2.34 update
Optimized the display logic for the actual game speed in the top right corner.
Fixed the issue of typing text too quickly while running IsaacSocket.
Updated compatibility with the latest IsaacSocket connection program.

Previous Updates in English will be shown in the whole mod description.

The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.</description>
    <version>1.51</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Pills"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Babies"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
