<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name> !Szx Chinese Console</name>
    <directory>szx_chinese_console</directory>
    <id>3001774454</id>
    <description>三只熊中文控制台/Szx Chinese Console

The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
-----------------------------------------------------------------
这是拥有诸多功能的控制台mod，要游玩本mod你需要把以撒的官方控制台在option.ini文件中关闭，并且进入游戏后，将你的全屏[F]、静音[M]、暂停[P]三个按键改为[F9][F10][F11]，以保证你能使用mod的正常功能。

具体的控制台功能详情，可以来看我的b站视频，视频讲解地会比较细致，也更加容易理解~

有任何问题欢迎联系我，祝大家玩的愉快！

更新日志：

v2.02更新
修复了v1.07版本更新带来的名称搜索超过两个单词搜不到的问题
进一步完善了151-250号道具的民间通俗叫法(已完善进度：t1-t189和c1-c250)
修改了大量中文输入时拼音显示结果的顺序

v2.01更新
增加了搜索列表中的mod道具和mod饰品(支持序号搜索，支持仅英文的名称搜素，支持全部五个条件名的条件搜索，支持仅英文的部分标签的标签搜索(active, passive, trinket, familiar, hearts, soulhearts, blackhearts, keys, coins, bombs, special))
增加了搜索列表中的mod卡牌和mod药丸(仅英文)
增加了5级道具的道具品质显示文本颜色
进一步完善了1-150号道具的民间通俗叫法(已完善进度：t1-t189和c1-c150)
修改了大量中文输入时拼音显示结果的顺序

v1.07更新
修复了搜索模块中结果为空后另加字段会覆盖前几个字段效果的问题

v1.06更新
修复了[s]或[stage]楼层转送指令在贪婪模式中显示错误的问题
增加了[s]或[stage]楼层转送指令的细分菜单搜索，支持中英双语
更改了15个中文输入时拼音显示结果的顺序

v1.05更新
修复了部分近战武器在蒙眼状态不会收回的问题，如妈刀、骨哥棒槌、里夏娃圣血吸管

v1.04更新
增加了[sp 6]或[spawn 6]可互动实体的细分菜单搜索，支持中英双语

v1.03更新：
修复了中文显示模式下sp或spawn指令的&quot;5.350.[num]+'的失效问题

v1.02更新：
增加道具品质彩色文字显示（原先均为白色）
修复了包含1个结果的中文标签‘非店主’搜索不到的问题
修复了包含5个结果的道具条件名chargetype的值错误的问题
更改包含5个结果的饰品英文标签'familiars'为'familiar', 与道具的'familiar'英文标签统一
更改包含1个结果的饰品英文标签'lucks'为'luck', 与道具的'luck'英文标签统一
更改了1个中文输入时拼音显示结果的顺序

v1.01更新：
修复[rep]与[repeat]命令和预期不一致的问题
修复游戏暂停控制台画面保留状态时能使用[LAlt]+[F1]或[F2]的问题

由于行数限制，完整的mod描述介绍将在讨论区中展示（中英双语）
-----------------------------------------------------------------
Changelog:

v2.02 update
Fixed the issue in version 1.07 update where name search with more than two words would not yield any results.
Optimized the Chinese nick names of collectibles. (Completed progress: t1-t189 and c1-c250)
Adjusted a huge number of pinyin results display order in the option box in Chinese input mode.

v2.01 update
Added mod collectibles and mod trinkets into the result box.(Index search supported. English-only name search supported. Conditional search fully supported including all five condition names. English-only label search partly supported(active, passive, trinket, familiar, hearts, soulhearts, blackhearts, keys, coins, bombs, special).)
Added mod cards and mod pills into the result box.(English-only)
Added the text color of collectibles with quality 5 in item quality display.
Optimized the Chinese nick names of collectibles. (Completed progress: t1-t189 and c1-c150)
Adjusted a huge number of pinyin results display order in the option box in Chinese input mode.

v1.07 update
Fixed an issue that the result reappeared when the result box was already empty if user added another search word.

v1.06 update
Fixed the problem of wrong informational texts in greed mode by command [s] or [stage].
Added search mode support for command [s] or [stage] in both Chinese and English.
Adjusted the order of 15 pinyin results in Chinese input mode.

v1.05 update
Fixed an issue where certain weapons wouldn't retract while blindfolded, such as Moms Knife, Bone Club and Sumptorium.

v1.04 update
Added search mode support for command [sp 6] or [spawn 6] in both Chinese and English.

v1.03 update
Fixed an issue where &quot;sp 5.350.[id]+&quot; or &quot;spawn 5.350.[id]+&quot; can not be displayed in the input box.

v1.02 update
Added colored text display for [F6] (It was white previously.)
Fixed the issue that '非店主' label can not be searched.
Fixed the issue that 'chargetype' condition had an unexpected value.
Replaced the 'familiars' label for five trinkets to 'familiar' to align with the 'familiar' label for collectibles.
Replaced the 'lucks' label for a trinket to 'luck' to align with the 'luck' label for collectibles.
Adjusted the order of one pinyin result in Chinese input mode.

v1.01 update
Resolved an issue where the [rep] or [repeat] command did not produce the expected effects.
Resolved an issue where the [LAlt]+[F1] or [LAlt]+[F2] command can be taken account in the console-display-remain state when game is paused.

The whole mod description in English or in Chinese locates in the discussion forum due to the line limit here.</description>
    <version>1.10</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Pills"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Babies"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
